<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DRUG PROFILE</string>
    <string name="drug_image">"image represents drug "</string>
    <string name="profile_name">CLOTRIMAZOLE LOTION</string>
    <string name="drug_composition">Enter drug composition: Clotrimazole, Base non aqueuse</string>
    <string name="drug_description">
        \nThis medication is used to treat vaginal yeast infections. Clotrimazole reduces vaginal burning, itching, and discharge that may occur with this condition. This medication is an azole antifungal. It works by stopping the growth of yeast (fungus) that causes the infection. The vaginal product comes in 2 forms (a vaginal cream or tablet). Some products come with a skin cream to be applied to the area around the outside of the vagina.Ask your doctor before using this medication for self-treatment if this is your first vaginal infection. This medication only works for vaginal fungal infections. You may have a different type of infection (such as bacterial vaginosis) and may need a different medication.If you have fever, chills, flu-like symptoms, stomach/abdominal pain, or a bad-smelling vaginal discharge, do not use this medication. Contact your doctor right away because these may be signs of a more serious infection.
        \nIf you are using the over-the-counter product to self-treat, read all directions on the product package before using this medication. If you have any questions, consult your pharmacist. If your doctor has prescribed this medication, use it as directed.Read the Patient Information Leaflet available with this product. Consult your doctor or pharmacist if you have any questions.This product is for vaginal use only. Wash your hands before and after use. Avoid contact of this product with your eyes. If it gets into your eyes, wash them right away with plenty of water. Call your doctor if eye irritation persists.Dosage is based on your medical condition and response to treatment. Use the medication usually once daily at bedtime for 1 to 7 nights depending on the product used, or as directed by your doctor.If using the vaginal cream, follow the package instructions on how to fill/use the applicator with the cream. Lie on your back with your knees toward your chest. Insert one applicator filled with cream into the vagina as far as it will comfortably go. Slowly press the plunger of the applicator in to apply the cream. Make sure to insert the correct cream for use inside the vagina, not the skin cream for use on the outer genital area (vulva).If using the vaginal tablet, you may use either the applicator or your finger to insert the tablet. Unwrap the tablet before use. Follow the package instructions on how to fill the applicator with the vaginal tablet. Lie on your back with your knees toward your chest. Insert the tablet or the applicator into the vagina as far as it will comfortably go. Slowly press the plunger of the applicator to release the tablet.If you have itching/burning around the outside of the vagina (vulva), apply the skin cream to that area usually once or twice a day for no more than 7 days. If you are using a product with only the vaginal cream, you may apply a small amount of the vaginal cream to the area.Continue to use this medication every day for the full time prescribed, even if symptoms disappear after a few days or if your menstrual period starts. Stopping the medication too soon may allow the yeast infection to return.
        \nDo not use tampons, douches, spermicides or other vaginal products while using this medication. Unscented sanitary napkins may be used for your menstrual period or to protect your clothing from leakage of the medication.Tell your doctor if your condition does not improve after 3 days or lasts more than 7 days. Tell your doctor if your infection returns within 2 months. You may need a different or additional medication to treat your condition.
    </string>
    <string name="button_text">SUBMIT</string>
</resources>